usimprints.com 2016-03-16

# Privacy Policy | USimprints

### Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy for this Website, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.

 **Information Collection**  
We collect personal information (such as your name, email address and any other details you provide to us that identifies you as an individual) from you when you submit a request for information or when you submit your details for any other reason. Personal information will only be collected with your consent.

When you browse our Website, we may also log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our Website you visit and how long you spend here. We do not link your IP address to any other personal information that you send to us. Like many other websites, we may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the Website (see section 6. Cookies).

Save for the use of cookies, we do not automatically log data or collect data apart from information you specifically provide to us.  
 **  
Use of Information We Collect**  
We will use your information for several general purposes including: fulfilling any requests for information or services placed by you, processing any other transactions authorizedby you, personalizingyour experience on our Website, keeping you up to date with news about USimprints, our products and services, and providing other information to you which we think you may find of interest. Your personal information shall not be used for any other purposes.

 **Who May Process Data**  
Your personal information may be processed by us in accordance with this privacy policy. We take all reasonable care to prevent any unauthorizedaccess to your personal data. Personal information will not be sold or transferred to unaffiliated third parties without your prior consent.

 **Security Measures**  
We are serious about guarding the security of your personal information that we have under our control from unauthorizedaccess, improper use and disclosure, unauthorizeddestruction or accidental loss. However we cannot guarantee the protection of your personal data as due to the nature of the Internet, the Website is theoretically accessible by any user of the World Wide Web. You should be aware that when you disclose personal information on the Website it may be collected by another user and may result in unsolicited messages from other Internet users.

 **Session Variables**  
Some sections of our website require your information to be stored in what's known as a session variable. Session variables exist for the length of your visit (or in the case of our client login, until you log out).

 **Access and Changes to your Personal Information**  
Upon request, we may provide you with a copy of the personal information which we hold about you (in return for a small fee). Please address requests to support@usimprints.com and insert "access request" as the subject heading.

At your request, we will use reasonable efforts to update / correct personal information previously submitted by you. You may also request that we cease processing the personal information we have about you and that we delete your personal information from our database or records. However, it may be impossible to delete your information without some residual information because of backups and records of deletions.

Please address your requests to change or delete your personal information to info@USimprints.com and insert "change details" or "unsubscribe" as appropriate as the subject heading.

We will only perform the activities outlined above to the extent that such activities will not compromise privacy or security interests.

 **Changes to this Policy**  
We may change this privacy policy from time to time. When such a change is made we will post a revised version on the Website. It is your responsibility to view this privacy policy from time to time to be aware of any such change. Your continued use of the Website will indicate your agreement to any such change.
